Mind the steps
Thanks
No need to be so polite now
What should I say then
Mrs Fu
Regretting it
No I just suddenly felt that Mrs Fu
Has a nice ring to it
We already got our marriage certificate
I need to make some things clear upfront
Right now I don't have
Gu Chuze's family background
Or a grand wedding like that
I don't need it
I saw enough of grand weddings just now
It was lively indeed
But no one actually asked if I wanted it
Then what is this for
To start over
And to never give myself
To someone unworthy again
Where to stay
You can't go back to the Su family
in a wedding dress
You'll easily get ambushed at a hotel
I walked out with too much swagger
That I forgot to change
I have a small but quiet place
Then I'll trouble Mr Fu
to take me in for a night
A night
The first night of our marriage
Let's count it as one night for now
Alright Mrs Fu calls the shots
What are you looking at
The onlookers are busier than
those at the wedding
So harsh